{
    "quiz":[
        {
            "cat": "Anime",
            "quizList": [
                {
                    "question": "What do you have to do with Pokemon?",
                    "options": [
                        "Snatch 'em all!",
                        "Fetch 'em all!",
                        "Catch 'em all!",
                        "Match 'em all!"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Catch 'em all!"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of Code Geass protagonist?",
                    "options": [
                        "Cornelia Li Britannia",
                        "Suzaku Kururugi",
                        "Nunnally Lamperouge",
                        "Lelouch Vi Britannia"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Lelouch Vi Britannia"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of Takao Kinomiya (Tyson Granger?'s Bayblade Bit-Beast name?",
                    "options": [
                        "Dragoon",
                        "Dranzer",
                        "Driger",
                        "Galman"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Dragoon"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which of the following is not an Eevee pokemon evolution?",
                    "options": [
                        "Jolteon",
                        "Flareon",
                        "Espeon",
                        "Empoleon"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Empoleon"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which guild Juvia Lockster belong before joining the Fairy Tail Guild?",
                    "options": [
                        "Phantom Lord",
                        "Lamia Scale",
                        "Twilight Ogre",
                        "Sabertooth"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Phantom Lord"
                }
                
            ]
        },
        {
            "cat": "Superhero",
            "quizList": [
                {
                    "question": "In the comics, who created Captain America's shield?",
                    "options": [
                        "Howard Stark",
                        "Myron MacLain",
                        "Tony Stark",
                        "George Lucas"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Myron MacLain"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many version of the Iron man armor had Tony Stark made?",
                    "options": [
                        "3",
                        "10",
                        "7",
                        "50"
                    ],
                    "answer": "50"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where did DC's Joker spend most of his time?",
                    "options": [
                        "Red Hood",
                        "Arkham Asylum",
                        "Prime Earth",
                        "Alternate Timelines"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Arkham Asylum"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which of the following is not a member of DC's 'Birds of prey'?",
                    "options": [
                        "Batgirl",
                        "Wonder Woman",
                        "Black Canary",
                        "Huntress"
                    ],
                    "answer":  "Wonder Woman"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which of the following is the place of origin of Wonder Woman?",
                    "options": [
                        "Abyssia",
                        "Umec",
                        "Atlantis",
                        "Themyscira"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Themyscira"
                }
                
            ]
        },
        {
            "cat": "Disney",
            "quizList": [
                {
                    "question": "Which Disney film includes the hit song 'Let it Go?'",
                    "options": [
                        "Cars",
                        "Rapunzel",
                        "Aladdin",
                        "Frozen"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Frozen"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What poisonous fruit did Snow White eat?",
                    "options": [
                        "Blueberry",
                        "Apple",
                        "Peach",
                        "Orange"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Apple"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which Disney Princess sings 'Once Upon a Dream'?",
                    "options": [
                        "Snow White",
                        "Aurora",
                        "Jasmine",
                        "Ariel"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Aurora"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the city-name in Ducktales?",
                    "options": [
                        "Duckworld",
                        "Duckburg",
                        "Duckearl",
                        "Duckport"
                    ],
                    "answer":  "Duckburg"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What's the name of Goofy's son?",
                    "options": [
                        "Mark Million Goof",
                        "Gaffy Goof",
                        "Geefy Goof",
                        "Maxmillion 'Max' Goof"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Maxmillion 'Max' Goof"
                }
                
            ]
        },
        {
            "cat": "Animated Series",
            "quizList": [
                {
                    "question": "What type of bird can Wile E. Coyote Never Catch?",
                    "options": [
                        "An Emu",
                        "An Ostrich",
                        "A Kiwi",
                        "A Roadrunner"
                    ],
                    "answer": "A Roadrunner"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What sort of animal is Pepe le Pew in Looney Tunes?",
                    "options": [
                        "Skunk",
                        "Racoon",
                        "Cat",
                        "Mongoose"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Skunk"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which of the following was not a Hanna-Barbera cartoon?",
                    "options": [
                        "Quick Draw McGraw",
                        "Speed Racer",
                        "Scooby-Doo",
                        "Jonny Quest"
                    ],
                    "answer": "Speed Racer"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the Flintstones' pet dinosaur?",
                    "options": [
                        "Dingo",
                        "Dino",
                        "Dinamo",
                        "Domino"
                    ],
                    "answer":  "Dino"
                },
                {
                    "question": "which of the following is the power of Ghostfreak from Ben 10?",
                    "options": [
                        "Possession",
                        "Invisibility",
                        "Body Alteration",
                        "All of the above"
                    ],
                    "answer": "All of the above"
                }
                
            ]
        }
    ]
}